ethiocinema.com 2013-07-27

# Privacy Policy

**Last modified: February 24, 2013**

Ethiocinema.com is established to promote Ethiopia. We share videos from other websites through an embed code. When you share information with us, for example by commenting on our page or take occasional polls, we can make our services even better. As you use our services, we want you to be clear how we’re using information and the ways in which you can protect your privacy.

**Our Privacy Policy explains:**

-What information we collect and why we collect it.  
-How we use that information.  
-The choices we offer, including how to access and update information.

We’ve tried to keep it as simple as possible, but if you’re not familiar with terms like [cookies](http://www.whatarecookies.com/), [IP addresses](http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/IP_address), [pixel tags](https://www.facebook.com/help/236257763148568) and [browsers](http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Web_browser), then read about these key terms first by clicking on them. Your privacy matters to Ethiocinema so whether you are new to our website or a long-time user, please do take the time to get to know our practices – and if you have any questions [contact us](http://www.ethiocinema.com/contact-us-2/).

**Information we collect**

We collect information to provide better services to all of our users 

_**We collect information in two ways:**_

_-Information you give us._  
We collect occasional polls to understand our users and help advertisers reach out a targeted ad group. In addition to that, we have comment section you may use to express your opinion. Any email you send us through our contact us page might also be information we collect from you to make our service better.

_-Information we get from your use of our services._  
Ethiocinema uses google analytic and Daily stat applications in order to monitor visitor number, location, and system usages such as browser type and key words searched. In addition to that, we collect location and IP address information whenever you rate a content on our website.

**Cookies and anonymous identifiers**

We use various technologies to collect and store information when you visit our web page, and this may include sending one or more cookies or anonymous identifiers to your device. We also use cookies and anonymous identifiers when you interact with services we offer to our partners, such as advertising services or Google features that may appear on other sites.

**How we use information we collect**

We use the information we collect from our website to provide, maintain and improve it, to develop new features, and to protect any illegal activities. We also use this information to offer you tailored content – like giving you more relevant search results and ads.

When you contact Ethiocinema, we may keep a record of your communication to help solve any issues you might be facing. We may use your email address to inform you about our services, such as letting you know about upcoming changes or improvements.

We use information collected from cookies and other technologies, like pixel tags, to improve your user experience and the overall quality of our services. For example, by saving your IP location, we’ll be able to deliver relevant ads tailored to your location. When showing you tailored ads, we will not associate a cookie or anonymous identifier with sensitive categories, such as those based on race, religion, sexual orientation or health.

We will ask for your consent before using information for a purpose other than those that are set out in this Privacy Policy.  
Ethiocinema processes collected information on our servers in the US. 

**Control who you share information with.**

You may also set your browser to block all cookies, including cookies associated with our services, or to indicate when a cookie is being set by us. However, it’s important to remember that many of our services may not function properly if your cookies are disabled. 

**Information we share**

We do not share personal emails and emails with companies, organizations and individuals outside of Ethiocinema unless one of the following circumstances apply:

-With your consent

We will share personal information with companies, organizations or individuals outside of Ethiocinema when we have your consent to do so. We require opt-in consent for the sharing of any sensitive personal information.

-For external processing such as Google analytic 

We provide personal information to our affiliates or other trusted businesses or persons to process it for us, based on our instructions and in compliance with our Privacy Policy and any other appropriate confidentiality and security measures.

-For legal reasons

We will share personal information with companies, organizations or individuals outside of Ethiocinema if we have a good-faith belief that access, use, preservation or disclosure of the information is reasonably necessary to:

meet any applicable law, regulation, legal process or enforceable governmental request.  
enforce applicable Terms of Service, including investigation of potential violations.  
detect, prevent, or otherwise address fraud, security or technical issues.  
protect against harm to the rights, property or safety of Ethiocinema, our users or the public as required or permitted by law.

If Ethiocinema is involved in a merger, acquisition or asset sale, we will continue to ensure the confidentiality of any personal information and give affected users notice before personal information is transferred or becomes subject to a different privacy policy.

**Application**

Our Privacy Policy does not apply to services offered by other companies or individuals, including sites that may be displayed to you in search results, sites that may include video or any services, or other sites linked from our services. Our Privacy Policy does not cover the information practices of other companies and organizations who advertise our services, and who may use cookies, pixel tags and other technologies to serve and offer relevant ads.

**Enforcement**

We regularly review our compliance with our Privacy Policy. We also adhere to several self regulatory frameworks. When we receive formal written complaints, we will contact the person who made the complaint to follow up. We work with the appropriate regulatory authorities, including local data protection authorities, to resolve any complaints regarding the transfer of personal data that we cannot resolve with our users directly.

**Changes**

Our Privacy Policy may change from time to time. We will not reduce your rights under this Privacy Policy without your explicit consent. We will post any privacy policy changes on this page.
